(Bernadette:)You heard what he said
about his parents.
(Bernadette:)It was the little things
they kept bottled up.
(Bernadette:)I don't want that
to happen to us.
(Howard:)How can I convince you it won't?
(Bernadette:)Well, is there anything about me
you're keeping inside?
(chuckles)
I'm not answering that.
(Howard:)It's a trap.
So there are things
you don't like.
(Howard:)And here I am in the trap.
(Howard:)You just keep talking.
(Howard:)I'm gonna chew my leg off.
(Bernadette:)Just tell me one thing
that bothers you,
(Bernadette:)and I promise I won't get mad.
(Howard:)Okay. The truth is...
(Howard:)sometimes... you're too...
(Howard:)beautiful.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Bernadette:)Howie, be serious.
(Howard:)Okay, okay.
(Howard:)I really don't like
(Howard:)how your wings poke me
when we sleep
(Howard:)'cause you're an angel.
(Bernadette:)Okay, fine,
maybe it was a bad idea.
(Howard:)I just don't think the secret
to a happy marriage